http://www.americanframe.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
American Frame is committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Our privacy policy, which was updated on October 20, 2016, addresses the information we collect and how it is used to enhance your shopping experience. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform what type of contact information we may collect from you, how we may use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of the information.
If you have any privacy-related comments or questions, please contact us via email at privacy@americanframe.com.
As part of our commitment to your privacy, American Frame supports and adheres to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise to American Consumers." We have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers' requests not to share their information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone or other solicitations from American Frame Corporation.
Information such as name, street and email address, telephone number, site navigation history and credit card information may be collected when you:
Order through our website, catalog or Showroom store
Contact us via phone or email
Request a catalog
Subscribe to our E-Tip newsletter
Create an account at americanframe.com
Participate in a survey, promotion or educational event
Information you provide may be used to:
Complete your transaction
Confirm and track your order
Contact you by email or regular mail regarding your order
Mail marketing materials
Email the E-Tip Newsletter
Enhance your shopping experience
Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any contact information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain addresses from which people visit us and analyze this data for preferences, trends, and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.
Customer information, except for credit card data which falls under PCI industry standards, is maintained in a secure server along with your purchase history for an undetermined period of time.
Periodically we may establish business relationships with other outside persons or entities who we believe trustworthy and with privacy policies consistent with ours. In such cases, we may rent, exchange, cross reference or share information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online, in our Showroom or through our catalog. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our service partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate about our products and events that may be of interest to you and for other promotional purposes.
Additionally, we may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc, and we provide these partners with the information needed for them to perform such services. We also ask them to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to American Frame or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.
Marketing Communications
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from our service partners, or if you would like to opt out of our rental or exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know by calling 1.800.537.0944 or by email at privacy@americanframe.com. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specify what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other contact information, please contact us the same way.
Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.
Cookies
Information is gathered through the use of “cookies” and/or other online tools. A cookie is simply a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer. They allow us to remember browsing and shopping cart actions, recognize a revisiting user, track your status in our promotions, contests, sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns, and to customize content to suit your preferences. In order to complete a transaction at americanframe.com, your cookies must be enabled on your computer. If your browser is set to refuse cookies, please call us at (800) 537-0944, M-F 8:30 – 5:30 pm EST, to place an order.
Security
American Frame Corporation has physical security in our server facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our site's order process uses industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. The process requires users to give us contact and financial information. We use this information to fulfill your order. Any and all information submitted in these forms will be held in strictest confidence and not shared with any other business entity outside of your Credit Card Service and/or your Bank. We do reserve the right to contact you to answer questions, offer suggestions, and make corrections to your order. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our website, and you do so at your own risk.
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18.
We recommend that you keep your account information and password in a safe place and that you do not share it with anyone. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are using a shared computer or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.
Policy Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part we will inform you by posting a notice on our website and our social media channels. We may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. Please be sure to review our privacy policy periodically.
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may email us or call us at 1.800.537.0944. Effective Date: June 1, 2010
Intellectual Property
Unless otherwise noted, all materials, including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips, and written and other materials that appear as part of this site (collectively, the "Contents") are the intellectual property of American Frame Corporation and protected by copyright, trademark trade dress and/or other intellectual property laws. The Contents are owned, controlled or licensed by American Frame Corporation. The site as a whole is protected by copyright and trade dress, all worldwide rights, titles and interests in and to which are owned by American Frame Corporation.
You may not download, copy, reproduce, publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the site, or any related software.
